exports.basicQuestions = [
	{
		front: 'United States did not enter ww2 until after the Japanese bombed where in Hawaii, on December 7, 1941',
		back: 'Pearl Harbor'
	},
	{
		front: 'Adolf Hitler was born in the city of Lintz in which country near the German border.',
		back: 'Austria'
	},
	{
		front: 'JFK was assassinated while driving through what city on November 1963.',
		back: 'Dallas'
	},
	{
		front: 'Who was the commanding general of the Battle of New Orleans in 1815.',
		back: 'Andrew Jackson'
	},
	{
		front: 'Who famously stated "I shall return" after leaving Bataan in 1942 fleeing from the conquering Japanese. He in fact did return.',
		back: 'Douglas MacArthur'
	},
	{
		front: 'The American involvement in the Korean war lasted until.',
		back: '1953'
	},
	{
		front: 'The Battle of Hastings in 1066 was fought in what country?',
		back: 'England'
	},
	{
		front: 'What document was created in 1215 issued by King John I of England. It was a document that signed away much of the royal power and is one of the first major political documents.',
		back: 'Magna Carta'
	},
	{
		front: 'Who was a German goldsmith and printer who is credited with inventing movable type printing in Europe around 1439, and mechanical printing globally.',
		back: 'Gutenberg'
	},
	{
		front: 'What illness was carried by fleas on rats aboard trading ships from the East and ravaged Europe for many centuries.',
		back: 'Bubonic Plague'
	},
	{
		front: 'The Hundred Years War was fought between England and what country?',
		back: 'France'
	},
	{
		front: 'The best-preserved section of the Great Wall was built in the 14th through 17th centuries A.D., during the what dynasty?',
		back: 'Ming'
	},
	{
		front: 'Who was concerned over the indulgence policy of the Catholic church would become the father of the Protestant movement in Europe.',
		back: 'Martin Luther'
	},
	{
		front: 'In 1594 Shakespeare became an actor and a playwright in the company of what Theatre.',
		back: 'Globe'
	},
	{
		front: 'The Khmer Rouge was a regime ruling what country in the 20th century.',
		back: 'Cambodia'
	},
	{
		front: 'Who was a famous 5th century A.D conqueror who was known as "The Scourge of God"',
		back: 'Atilla the Hun'
	},
	{
		front: 'What makers model 1873 lever action rifle was a revolutionary firearm that is known as "The Gun that Won the West".',
		back: 'Winchester'
	},
	{
		front: 'Who was the first Western explorer to reach China.',
		back: 'Marco Polo'
	}
	]